Guide to the William Ballard Hoyt papers, 1878-1881.
Hoyt, William Ballard papers, 1878-1881.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
William Ballard Hoyt papers, 1878-1881.
37-5-563
William Ballard Hoyt, 1858-1915.
.1 cubic ft.
Notebooks and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Notebooks kept and letters written by Hoyt concerning class work and athletics.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell University Class of 1881.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Notebooks kept and letters written by Hoyt concerning class work and athletics.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hoyt, William Ballard, 1858-1915.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University. Class of 1881.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Student notebook kept by William B. Hoyt: notes on psychology course and also on "Warfare between Ecclesiasticism and the Political, Mental and Moral Sciences" by Andrew D. White, c. 1880-1881 (Box 1)
- Small notebook containing few notes on crew and rowing and other miscellaneous entries (Box 1)
- Small notebook containing miscellaneous entries such as small accounts, what appear to be lecture notes, etc. (Box 1)
- Letter, dated Apr. 14, from William Channing Russell to George Burr about his leaving Cornell [removed to Burr Papers, May 1990 per EE], 1881 (Box 1)
- Letter, dated September, to Dr. F. L. O. Roehrig (written in Latin) [removed to separate collection, per EE], 1881 (Box 1)
- Letter, dated February 1, from William B. Hoyt to his brother Albert H. Hoyt; also postcard Oct. 12 (?), 1880 (Box 1)
- Letter, dated Feb. 15, from William B. Hoyt to his parents, 1880 (Box 1)
- Letter, dated June 2, from Hoyt to his mother, 1881 (Box 1)
- Letter, dated Nov. 24, commencing "Dear Mother" but letter is either unfinished or not signed, 1878 (Box 1)
- Printed circular letter, dated January 31, from New York Association of Cornell University, 1882 (Box 1)
- 2 printed receipts for money, 1882 (Box 1)